crunchyfashion.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Crunchy Fashion Pvt .Ltd.

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for CrunchyFashion. We are committed to protecting your privacy and encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we protect the information you disclose to us.

If you believe that CrunchyFashion is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, please contact us at info@crunchyfashion.com

###  Information collection and use

CrunchyFashion is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. CrunchyFashion collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

We recognize and respect your need for privacy and security as you visit our site. When you visit our Website, We may require Customers who visit our Website and purchase products on our Website to give us contact information, which may include but is not limited to the Customer's name, company name, address, phone number, email address, cookies, IP logs, billing information, billing name and address, credit card number and other Personal information as needed. Besides the Personal Information, we may also collect other information regarding your use of the Website.  From time to time, we may also collect or ask for additional Personal Information, which will also be expressly included herein as Personal Information.  You can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it when asked or not using the Website, although not providing it may hinder your ability to use the Website.

Information collected is used to provide and maintain the Website and is used at CrunchyFashion's discretion. This Information can also be used to contact you to further discuss interest in our company, the services we provide, and to send information regarding CrunchyFashion, its partners, its products and other activities such as promotions and events.  You may be invited to receive email correspondence by providing an email address.  Your email address and any Personal Information will not be distributed or shared with third parties unless it is to transact such business as you have contracted us to do, to comply with legal processes and/or law enforcement requests, or to conduct any business as CrunchyFashion, in its sole discretion, deems reasonable.

In general, you can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We acknowledge that you have the right to control how your Personal Information is collected and used.

###  Information sharing

CrunchyFashion gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. CrunchyFashion will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested service, such as outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services.

We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the site to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of the assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) relating to CrunchyFashion.

Finally, notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we believe that we are required to do so (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (iii) to enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) to protect our operations or those of any affiliated entities; (v) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of CrunchyFashion, any affiliated entities, you or others; and (vi) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

###  Security

CrunchyFashion strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Your Personal Information and to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. For this purpose, CrunchyFashion adopts internal reviews of the data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where CrunchyFashion stores Your personal data.

CrunchyFashion is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive Your Personal Information. The Website also linked to many other sites and we are not/shall be not responsible for their privacy policies or practices as it is beyond our control.

###  Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie from our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the web site that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer.

###  Surveys & Sweepstakes

From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and e-mail address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

###  Changes to this policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the site, without prior notice. You can determine when this privacy policy was last revised by referring to date at the top of this page. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Internet, accessible through the site. Use of the site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy then in effect. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to ensure familiarity with our most current version.
